troptiontrading.com 2011-09-16

# Privacy Statement | Troption Trading

Privacy Statement:

TroptionTrading.com privacy notice

GlobalTroption Partners, Inc. (“gtp.dobarter.com”) has written this

statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting

your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and

dissemination practices for this website. As this policy may change

from time to time, please check back periodically.

Troptiontrading.com uses the information we collect about you to process orders.

When you register at Troptiontrading.com, we collect your name, email addresses,

mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date in order to

process and fulfill your order. In some instances, products ordered at

Troptiontrading.com are shipped directly from our vendors, and some of your

information is shared with these vendors to enable them to fulfill and

ship your order.

When you sign up for Troptiontrading.com Auction Alerts, we need only an email

address to send you the email topics that you have selected. We also

use your email address to send you email notice of your bid and order

status, and we may use your email address to send you notice of

upgrades or changes to Troptiontrading.com, new services, and special offers. You

may choose not to receive any of these emails when you register, or at

a later date, by accessing Troptiontrading.com Auction Alerts.

We occasionally will ask for additional information from you. For

instance, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address in

connection with a contest or other promotional feature in which you

participate, so we can administer the contest and notify winners. We

may offer contests or promotions with third parties; policies

concerning use of your personal data gathered in connection with any

such contest or promotion will be specifically set forth in the rules

and policies applicable to the contest or promotion.

Troptiontrading.com offers a service called “Tell a Friend” that allows you to

notify friends about open auctions. If you choose to use our referral

service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your

friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your

friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We do

not save or share your buddies email address, they are only used for

this one time mailing. Please note, however, that Troptiontrading.com opposes the

practice of sending unsolicited commercial emails, also known as

“spam”. Therefore, we request that you send “Tell A Friend” emails

only to people known by you who may be interested in the auction. If

someone asks you not to send these emails to him or her, please

comply.

When you bid on an item, you must enter the amount of your bid, your

Troptiontrading.com Login ID and your password. Only your initials, city and

state and your bid will be publicly available in the Current Winning

Bids history.

Recognizing the global nature of the Internet, you agree to comply

with all applicable local laws and rules regarding online conduct and

privacy, as well as content. Specifically, but not as a limitation,

you agree to comply with all applicable laws regarding transmission of

technical and personal data exported from the United States or the

country in which you reside.

Cookies

“Cookies” are pieces of information that are passed to your browser

and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Troptiontrading.com uses cookies to

recognize repeat visitors, to automatically enter your login ID in our

bid form, and to provide additional features to make bidding & buying

at Troptiontrading.com easier and more efficient. If you do not wish to receive

cookies, you can turn them off using your browser’s settings . We do

not link the information we store in cookies to any personally

identifiable information you submit while on our site.

Sharing data with third parties

Upon registration with Troptiontrading.com each of our customers is

assigned a random and anonymous customer number, which we use to track

customer orders. This customer number is different from any custom

login ID selected by you and may be passed to third party vendors with

whom we work to provide more efficient and relevant services to our

users. Our anonymous customer numbers may be used to measure traffic

and visiting patterns on Troptiontrading.com and on other websites on the

Internet. We may also compile statistics and other data about our

customers on an aggregated basis, and may share such aggregated data

with selected third parties. Troptiontrading.com can (and you authorize us to)

release any information about you when we believe that such release is

reasonably necessary to comply with law, enforce or apply the terms of

any of our user agreements, enforce other Troptiontrading.com rights, or protect

the rights, property or safety of Troptiontrading.com, the Troptiontrading.com Web site, our

users, or others. Further, as permitted by applicable law, Troptiontrading.com

can (and you authorize us to) disclose your login ID, name, street,

address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email, company

and any other information in connection with an investigation of

fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy or other unlawful

activity whenever Troptiontrading.com in its sole discretion believes necessary

or appropriate. In the event GlobalTroption Partners, Inc. goes

through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by

another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your

personally identifiable information will likely be among assets

transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in

ownership or control of your personal information.

In addition, we may share information about you with third parties as

necessary to complete a transaction requested by you or to enable them

to provide special opportunities and offers to you. We may share

information about you with our business partners, affiliates or other

third parties with your approval only. If your personally identifiable

information changes, or if you no longer want us to share information

you provide with third parties, you may correct, update, or

unsubscribe by making the change in My Account located in My Page on

Troptiontrading.com

You may choose whether or not to receive Outbid and order processing

emails in My Account and in My Mailbox. By registering at Troptiontrading.com,

you consent to the collection and use of this information by Troptiontrading.com

for order processing, Auction Alert emails, or the sharing of your

personally identifiable information to our business partners (with

your consent only). In the event of changes in our privacy policy,

this page will be updated with the current information.

Links

This Web site may contain links to other web sites. We provide these

links for your convenience, but we do not review, control or monitor

the privacy practices of websites operated by others. We are not

responsible for the performance of these sites or for your business

dealings with them. Your use of other web sites is subject to the

terms and conditions of those web sites, including the privacy

policies of those web sites.

Children’s Privacy

This Web site is designed for an adult audience only, and children

should not use this Web site. We will not intentionally collect online

any personal information (such as a child’s name or e-mail address)

from children under the age of 18. If you think that we have collected

personal information from a child under the age of 18, please contact

us and we will address the issue.

Security

How your information is encrypted

There are certain areas on the site where you may enter and submit

additional information. Certain of these areas are encrypted using SSL

encrypted transmissions between your Web browser and our Web server.

This is designed to reduce the chance that someone (e.g. on your

network at work or at your Internet service provider) may try to

compromise your private information as it travels from your Web

browser to our secure server. You’ll know when transmitted data is

encrypted by a security notice when you enter an encrypted page, and

by the presence of an icon on your browser, either a key for Netscape

or a lock for Microsoft Internet Explorer. The pages where you submit

your account information, place a bid, and receive confirmation of a

successful bid are all encrypted. In order to keep the highest level

of security possible with your credit card information, we do not

store your full credit card number.

Protecting your login ID and password

Always keep your Troptiontrading.com account number and password secret. They are

your only identification for bidding purposes. If you receive

information about a bid you did not place, or questionable

communications regarding your account, please contact

TroptionTrading.com Customer Support immediately by email. One

potential way for someone to steal your login ID and password is if

you bookmark any area on MyPage or a bid submission page. This is a

concern if your browser is available to other people at work, home, or

especially if you use a browser at a public internet cafe. You should

not bookmark such pages and you should clear the browser cache and

quit the browser completely when you are done surfing

Troptiontrading.com We have also worked to protect you against such a

mistake. Even if someone obtains both your login ID and password, the

system is designed to restrict access to your credit card information

because that field is cleared when they log in to My Page.

About SSL, security, and firewall problems

Some older browsers (such as IE 3.0.2) have known SSL bugs. These can

result in the browser crashing on SSL pages or giving error messages.

We recommend that you upgrade to the latest version of whatever

browser you prefer. For AOL users, you may be able to upgrade your

security by downloading and replacing the schannel.dll from Microsoft.

For users behind corporate firewalls, you need to configure your web

browser security settings. This includes setting https or secure proxy

settings. To determine if you have such a security problem, you can

edit a secure URL, replacing ‘https’ (secure) with ‘http’ (insecure).

If the page works with http:// but not https://, then you have a

problem with your security settings. You should contact your system

administrator for assistance.

Technical Details About Encryption

Troptiontrading.com operates with a OS Commerce network, Paypal, and

Jrox Affiliates program.

GlobalTroption Partners, Inc. — 1011 Adams Street, WPB, FL 33407
